

# lyn.ly

## JUNIOR FRONT-END DEVELOPER

As a recent addition to the Web Development world, I am really excited to begin my journey as Junior Front-end Developer in an industry that constantly evolves and challenges you to never stop learning new things everyday. I am a problem solver and enjoy finding innovative solutions through code and design. I love seeing it all come to life on screen, and how simple elements can help guide and enhance a user's experience.

#### **CONTACT**

0410 482 122 lynda.ly1@gmail.com

lynly.github.io linkedin.com/in/lyndaly github.com/lynly

#### **EDUCATION**

#### **General Assembly**

Web Development Immersive, 2017

#### **Shillington College**

Shillington Web Course, 2014

#### **Shillington College**

Certificate IV in Design: CUV40303, 2011

#### **University of New South Wales**

Bachelor of Industrial Design, 2008

#### **SKILLS**

### **Front-End Web**

HTML, CSS, JavaScript, jQuery,

## **Back-End Web**

Ruby, Rails, Ajax, PostgreSQL

# Design

Adobe Creative Suite: InDesign, Illustrator, Photoshop.

#### **CAPABILITIES**

UX/UI Design Principles, Web Design, Wireframing, Print Design, Branding, Advertising, Marketing

## **DEMONSTRATED ABILITIES**

Attention to detail, Adaptable, Proactive, Team player, Autonomous, Performs well under pressure

# **EXPERIENCE**

**Web Development Immersive Student** | General Assembly | Sydney, Australia March 2017 – June 2017 (3 month Full-time)

Completed an intensive 3 month Full-time course, gaining knowledge of programming fundamentals, industry best practices for writing code, using version control, developing full-stack applications and working in collaborative teams.

FINAL PROJECT | Wireframe | wireframing-app.herokuapp.com

Drag and drop, wireframing application created for non-designers. It consisted of a simple graphical user interface that will allow web developers to quickly mock-up their ideas and focus on the basics. I also wanted to encourage the use of a 12-column-grid design system, that will help stylise the layout and the use of rows to guide the spacing on the page.

For more information on my projects, check out my portfolio at lynly.github.io

Creative Artworker | Charles Tyrwhitt | London, United Kingdom June 2016 - February 2017 (9 month Contract)

Responsible for deliverying key marketing collateral and campaigns across various international territories. Duties include preparing press ready artwork, ensuring accuracy of work at all times and liaising with the offsite repro-house.

**Artworker** | Addison group | London, United Kingdom February 2016 – May 2015 (4 month Contract)

Responsible for creating corporate reports for various leading brands following their branding guidelines and collating technically accurate production files. Worked along with creative services and designers for new content flow-in and support client amends.

**Brochure Artworker** | STA Travel | London, United Kingdom June 2015 - December 2015 (6 month Contract)

Responsible for creating brochure pages for the STA Travel brochure range following branding guidelines and page templates whilst maximising their aesthetic potential. Build, design and amend detailed maps to support brochure content.

**Graphic Designer and Creative Consultant** | John Sample Group | Sydney, Australia April 2012 - March 2015

Created the 2014 Branding Guidelines, further producing templates and redesigned websites implementing the new changes. Also, oversaw a junior, and became more involved in the design process from brief taking, conceptual development and liaising with marketing managers to producing finished artwork.